- Penny, wait.
- Yeah?
(Penny:)Um...
(Leonard:)If you don't have any other plans...
...do you wanna join us for Thai food
and a Superman movie marathon?
(Penny:)A marathon? Wow, how many
Superman movies are there?
(Sheldon:)You're kidding, right?
(Penny:)I do like the one where
Lois Lane falls from the helicopter...
...and Superman catches her.
(Penny:)- Which one was that?
- One.
You realize that scene was rife
with scientific inaccuracy?
(Penny:)Yes, I know, men can't fly.
(Sheldon:)No, let's assume that they can.
(Sheldon:)Lois Lane is falling.
(Sheldon:)Accelerating at an initial rate
of 32 feet per second.
(Sheldon:)Superman swoops down to save her
by reaching out two arms of steel.
Miss Lane, who is now traveling...
(Sheldon:)...at approximately
120 miles an hour, hits them...
(Sheldon:)...and is immediately
sliced into three equal pieces.
(Leonard:)Unless Superman
matches her speed and decelerates.
In what space, sir? In what space?
She's 2 feet above the ground.
(Sheldon:)If he really loved her,
he'd let her hit the pavement.
(Sheldon:)- It would be a more merciful death.
- That doesn't...